# Jaden Stittsworth

Test Automation Engineer

Pittsburgh, PA
(412) 527-4078

Jadenrs10@gmail.com

www.Jadenstittsworth.com

LinkedIn Profile

## PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am a Test Automation Engineer with significant experience creating Selenium driven UI frameworks using Cucumber Gherkin BDD and TDD along with creating Selenium driven backend testing frameworks using Rest Assured and jsonschema2pojo for encapsulating JSON Response. I've also designed and implemented the CI/CD architecture for containerized applications deployed through Jenkins. Using Jira to follow the process and reach the accurate requirements. Lastly, I have proven experience familiarizing myself and working within existing frameworks, as well as adapting or modifying them as circumstances require for reporting and technical usability.

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

## SysLibrary Test Automation Engineer / Remote : December 2020 - Present

6 month internship where I Maintained the Selenium Java automation framework and resources in source controls like GIT/GITHUB using AWS code Commits. Worked effectively in an AGILE Team with Project Management to achieve Selenium automation of high quality, while maintaining release deadlines and QA processes improvements. Participated in giving points to the Stories/Defects. I compared data with Front-end and Back-end information. Used Postman to make calls manually and used data to automate.

# FleetApps Test Automation Engineer / Remote : May 2020 - December 2020

6 month internship with similar daily activity to my current project focused on analysing SRS and UserStories. Then created test cases manually or by automating using Selenium. Mainly UI testing compared to my current project.

#### **EDUCATION**

# Cybertek Schools, Virginia (Online Student) — May 2020 - May 2021

Java Full Stack automation developer(SDET) program. Focused on training IT professionals from the ground up. Started basics of Java to Selenium to SQL and on. This program produces some of the sharpest Test Automation Engineers in the market.

# Mount Lebanon Highschool, Pittsburgh PA — August 2016 - June 2019

Graduated early with extensive real world experience sessions. Mt. Lebanon provided an unmatched education that prepared me for any career. I loved my AP Computer Science course with a passion and had to make it into a career.

### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Testing Tools: Selenium WebDriver, Selenium Grid, Rest Assured, JDBC, Appium

Framework: Cucumber, Behavior Driven Development, JUnit, TestNG, Hybrid, Data Driven Development, Page Object Model (POM), Karate, Serenity

Languages: Java, SQL, HTML, Gherkin, XML, JSON

Platform: Windows, Mac OS, AWS, Windows Server

IDE: IntelliJ, Eclipse, Postman, Sublime Text

Databases: Oracle, MySQL, PostgreSQL

Build Tool: Maven, Jenkins

Deployment: Git, GitHub

Methodologies: Agile/Scrum, Waterfall

Test Management: Jira, Jira XRAY

Testing Methods: Functional, Smoke, Regression

Language: English (Native)

#### **LEARNING**

Currently Studying for the Following:

AWS Cloud Practitioner Certification

OCA11 Certification